{
  "categories": [],
  "description": "Chemistry time! Based on the symbol, name the element.",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Hydrogen",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "H"
  }, {
    "answer": "Nitrogen",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "N"
  }, {
    "answer": "Oxygen",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "O"
  }, {
    "answer": "Gold",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "Au"
  }, {
    "answer": "Iron",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "Fe"
  }, {
    "answer": "Potassium",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "K"
  }, {
    "answer": "Helium",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "He"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lithium",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "Li"
  }, {
    "answer": "Sulfur",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "S"
  }, {
    "answer": "Silver",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "Ag"
  }, {
    "answer": "Carbon",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "C"
  }, {
    "answer": "Copper",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "Cu"
  }, {
    "answer": "Calcium",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "Ca"
  }, {
    "answer": "Sodium",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "Na"
  }, {
    "answer": "Uranium",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "U"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lead",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "Pb"
  }, {
    "answer": "Neon",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "Ne"
  }, {
    "answer": "Iodine",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "I"
  }, {
    "answer": "Silicon",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "Si"
  }, {
    "answer": "Mercury",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "Hg"
  }, {
    "answer": "Arsenic",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "As"
  }, {
    "answer": "Tin",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "Sn"
  }, {
    "answer": "Vanadium",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "V"
  }, {
    "answer": "Antimony",
    "category": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
    "question": "Sb"
  }],
  "quizLength": 24,
  "title": "Elements by Symbol Quiz",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/elements-by-symbol-quiz.php"
}